Partial Register of the Ronald MacArthur Hirst papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Stalingrad Files, 1929-2004 (Box 1-62)
  - Correspondence files, general and alphabetical
    - Rottiers, Geert, 2000-2002 (Box 31)
    - Sankei Shimbun (Tokyo), 1997 (Box 31)
    - Spiegel, Der, 1992 (Box 31)
    - Suda, Siegfried, 2002 (Box 31)
    - Turnbull, Keith
      - 1973-1989 (Box 31)
      - 1990-2003 (Box 31)
    - Uhle-Wettler, Franz, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
    - U.S. Army Military History Institute, 1983-1990 (Box 31)
    - Ussik, Boris (Museum-Panorama, Volgograd), 2003-2004 (Box 31)
    - Veuve, Jacqueline, 1982-1983 (Box 31)
    - Volksbund Deutsche Kriegsgräberfürsorge, e.V., 1972-2004 (Box 31)
    - Wahlbom, Makan, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Webster, George, 1984-1988 (Box 31)
    - Welt am Sonntag, 1989-1992 (Box 31)
    - Welt, Die, 1973-1983 (Box 31)
    - Wiese, Klaus, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Wijers, Hans, 1996-2002 (Box 31)
    - Zeit, Die, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Note cards
    - Index (Box 32)
    - Individual veterans, alphabetic by name (Box 32)
      - A-L (Box 32)
      - M-Z (Box 33)
    - Generals, alphabetic by name (Box 33)
      - Angern-Bässler (Box 33)
      - Daniels-Wulz (Box 34)
    - Army groups and divisions (Box 34)
    - Subjects, and unsorted (Box 35)
  - Photographs
    - Stalingrad veterans, alphabetic by name (Box 36)
      - A (Box 36)
      - B (Box 36)
      - C (Box 36)
      - D (Box 36)
      - E-F (Box 36)
      - G (Box 36)
      - H (Box 36)
      - I (Box 36)
      - J (Box 36)
      - K (Box 36)
      - L (Box 36)
      - M-N (Box 36)
      - O (Box 36)
      - P (Box 36)
      - R (Box 36)
      - S (Box 36)
      - T (Box 36)
      - U-V-W (Box 36)
      - Z (Box 36)
    - Unidentified (Box 36)
    - Visits by Hirst to veterans, 1969-1985 (Box 36)
    - Collections of photographs from various veterans or their families
      - Banzhaf, Fritz (Box 37)
      - Binder, Karl (Box 37)
      - Boriss, Martin (Box 37)
      - Burkhard, Hermann (Box 37)
      - Canstein, Werner von (Box 37)
      - Detten, Gustav von (Box 37)
      - Dropmann, Hermann (Box 37)
      - Harbeck (Box 37)
      - Heintz, Karl-Georg (Box 37)
      - Humbert, Gerhard (Box 37)
      - Keiner, Franz (Box 37)
      - Kutzschenbach, Achim von (Box 37)
        - Belgian surrender, 1940 (Box 37)
        - French surrender, 1940 (Box 37)
        - Stalingrad (Box 37)
      - Lang, Karl (Box 37)
      - Linden, Josef (Box 37)
      - Lüde, Walter von (Box 37)
      - Otte, Hans-Jürgen (Box 37)
      - Reimer, Erich (Box 37)
      - Schlessmann, Hermann (2 folders) (Box 37)
      - Schmid-Lossberg, Karl (Box 37)
      - Schmidt, Hermann (Box 37)
      - Selle, Herbert (Box 37)
      - Seydlitz, Walther von (Box 37)
      - Waldersee, Alfred (Box 37)
      - Zank, Horst (Box 37)
      - Zielisch, Hans (Box 37)
      - Zimmermann, Georg (Box 37)
    - Group photos, unknown provenance (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous reproductions (Box 38)
    - Published photographs (Box 38)
    - Reunions of veterans (Box 38)
      - Limburg (Box 38)
        - 1970-1972 (Box 38)
        - 1978 (Box 38)
        - 1980-1988 (Box 38)
      - Various (Box 38)
    - Scenes from Stalingrad, various (Box 38)
    - Scrapbook, unidentified (Box 38)
    - Stalingrad collage, assembled by Hirst, 1972 (Box 38)
    - Stalingrad Madonna, dedication of, at Coventry Cathedral, England, 1990 (Box 38)
    - Various archival documents, most unidentified (Box 39)
    - Various rolls of copy negatives (of above photographs) (Box 39)
    - Various veterans, numbered and identified by Hirst (Box 39)
  - Subject files
    - Abwehr Süd (copies from documents at U.S. National Archives) (Box 40)
    - Addresses, Armee-Oberkommando 6 (correspondence in tracking down survivors) (Box 40)
    - Aerial photographs of Stalingrad (Box 40)
    - "Alphabetical Directory" of German wartime leaders, unknown provenance (Box 40)
    - "Am Rande der Strassen: Atlas deutscher Kriegsgräber" (Box 40)
    - Ammerwald / Plansee (internment camp for families of Stalingrad officers) (Box 40)
    - Armee-Oberkommando 6 (AOK6), rosters (Box 40)
    - Army, German, lists of commanding officers, from published sources (Box 40)
      - 1929 (Box 40)
      - 1936 (Box 40)
      - 1939 (Box 40)
    - Block VI (German prisoners-of-war in Soviet camp, Jelabuga) (Box 40)
    - Book excerpts, arranged alphabetically by author (Box 40)
      - A-G (Box 40)
      - H-Z (Box 41)
    - Chaplains, Armee-Oberkommando 6 (Box 41)
    - Concentration of Russian Troops for Stalingrad Offensive (U.S. Army translation of German report) (Box 41)
    - Commanders (Box 41)
    - Counter Intelligence Corps, U.S. Army (copies of dossier kept on Friedrich von Paulus, 1947-1956) (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Division insignia (Box 41)
    - Enemy at the Gates (film) (Box 41)
      - 2001 (Box 41)
      - 2002 (Box 41)
    - Evacuees (Box 42)
    - Der Feldzug in Russland: Ein Operativer Ueberblick, by Gotthard Henrici (copy from U.S. Army, Europe, Historical Division) (Box 42)
    - Field Marshals (Box 42)
    - Fischer, Johannes, "Über den Entschluss zur Luftversorgung Stalingrads," 1969 (Box 42)
    - General Staff (Generalstab) (Box 42)
    - Generals (Box 42)
      - Identification cards (copies) (Box 42)
      - Notes compiled by Hirst, alphabetic by general (Box 42)
        - A-L (Box 42)
        - M-Z (Box 42)
      - Various documents (copies) (Box 42)
    - The German Air Force Versus Russia, U.S. Air Force Historical Study, Number 154, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Maps (3 folders) (Box 43)
    - National Komitee Freies Deutschland (Box 43)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 43)
    - Personnel records, Germany Army (from U.S. National Archives) (Box 43)
    - Position of 6th Army (notes and copied documents) (Box 43)
      - October-November 1942 (Box 43)
      - February 1943 (Box 44)
    - Radical Turning Point in the Course of the Great Patriotic War (excerpts from Soviet history of World War II, U.S. Army translation) (Box 44)
    - Red Air Force (Box 44)
    - Red Army (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Reverses on the Southern Wing (U.S. Army translation of German report) (Box 44)
    - Romanians (Box 44)
    - Russia tour, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Suzdal (Box 44)
    - Swiss medical mission (Box 44)
    - Veterans, miscellaneous information, alphabetically arranged by name (Box 45)
    - Walli III (Box 45)
    - War diaries (translated excerpts) (Box 45)
    - Zaitsev, Vasili (Box 45)
    - 48th Armored Division (XXXXVIII Panzer Korps) (Box 45)
  - Veterans associations (Box 45)
    - Bund Ehemaliger Stalingradkämpfer (Box 45)
    - Archives, proposed, 2002 (Box 45)
    - Christmas letters, 1963-1993 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1997 (Box 45)
    - Reunions (Limburg)
      - 1958-1986 (Box 45)
      - 1988 (Box 46)
      - 1990 (Box 46)
      - 1992 (Box 46)
      - 1994 (Box 46)
      - 1996 (Box 46)
      - 1998 (Box 46)
      - 2000 (Box 46)
      - 2002 (Box 46)
    - Kameradschaft der ehemaligen Nebel- und Werfertruppe, 1977-1986 (Box 46)
    - Kameradschaftsbund 16. Panzer und Infanterie Division (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1978 (Box 46)
      - Newsletter, "Unsere 16.,", 1991-1995 (Box 46)
    - Stalingradbund Österreich (Box 46)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1997 (Box 46)
      - Newsletters, 1983-1996 (Box 46)
    - Various organizations, 1970 (Box 47)
    - Newsletters and other publications
      - Anschriftenliste (44th Infantry Division), 1985-1990 (Box 47)
      - Brandenburger Kreuz und Quer (PzGrenBtl 43/3), 1991-1993 (Box 47)
      - Der Eisbär meldet (24th Infantry Division), 1990 (Box 47)
      - Falke-Mitteilungsblatt (29th Infantry and Armored Divisions)
        - 1951-1958 (Box 47)
        - 1980-1988 (Box 47)
        - 1994-2000 (Box 47)
      - Festschrift, 40. Jahrestag Aufstellung der 183 I.D., 1979 (Box 47)
      - Das Kleeblatt (71st Infantry Division), 1991-1993 (Box 47)
      - Mitteilungsblatt der Ehemaligen Elfer (11th Infantry Regiment, Saxony) (Box 47)
        - 1962-1979 (Box 47)
        - 1998-2001 (Box 47)
      - Mitteilungsblatt der Kameradschaft der 2. Wiener Division sowie der 44. Infanterie Division (44th Infantry Division), 1991-1993 (Box 47)
      - Tapfer und Treu, Treffen der 79 I.D., 1953-1965 (Box 47)
      - Unsere 16. (16th Infantry Division), 1991-1995 (Box 47)
      - Die 3. Infanterie Division im Zweiten Weltkrieg, Gerhard Dieckhoff (Box 47)
      - Die 384. Infanterie Division (Box 47)
      - Die 79. Infanterie-Division im Kampf um Stalingrad (Box 48)
      - 94. Infanterie Division
        - Die erste Eisenbahn der Nachrichten-Abteilung, Major Dr. Franz Muth (Box 48)
        - Nachrichten-Abteilung 194, Dr. Franz Muth, Kdr., Zur Person, 1984 (Box 48)
        - Erinnerungsbuch der 94. Infanterie Division (2 folders), 1982-1985 (Box 48)
      - Beiträge zur Geschichte der 60. Infanterie Division (Mot.), 1979 (Box 48)
        - Teil 1, Berichte (Box 48)
        - Teil 2, Karten, Bilder (Box 48)
        - Teil 3, Aus der Nachrichtenabteilung (Box 48)
      - Beobachtungs-Abteilung 36., Mainz-Stalingrad, 1970 (Box 48)
      - Geschichte des 11. (Sächsische) Infanterie-Regiments... von 1918-1945, undated (Box 49)
  - Veterans Memoirs
    - Boje, Arthur (?), copies, unknown provenance (Box 49)
    - Kurz, Georg, "3002 Tage Russland: Erinnerungen an meine Kriegs- und Gefangenenjahre,", 1987 (Box 49)
    - Probst, Josef, "Von Stalingrad nach Saratow,", undated (Box 49)
    - Strecker, Karl, "Von Moskau bis Ischia,", 1974 (Box 49)
    - Wolf, Richard, "Im Kampf um Stalingrad,", undated (Box 49)
    - Wolff, Ludwig, "Zwischen den Kriegen," and "Erinnerungen an Ludwig Wolff" (Box 49)
    - Stalingrad: Kessel und Gefangenschaft, by Horst Zank (typescript), 1991 (Box 49)
- Berlin Airlift Commemoration, 1947-2004 (Box 50-63)
  Correspondence, newspaper clippings, newsletters, photographs, printed material, sketches, arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  - Airmen
    - Boyd, Ralph, 1984-1999 (Box 50)
    - Burns, George S., 1998-2001 (Box 50)
    - Crites, Harry R., 1983-2000 (Box 50)
    - De Volentine, Joel, 1983-1999 (Box 50)
    - Diltz, Edwin, 1983-2001 (Box 50)
    - Erickson, Eugene, 1983-2000 (Box 51)
    - Hagen, Karl (Box 51)
      - Correspondence, 1984-2001 (Box 51)
      - Documents (Box 51)
    - Hargis, Frank, 1983-2001 (Box 51)
    - Heinig, Herbert, 1983-1999 (Box 51)
    - Howard, William R., 1983-2000 (Box 51)
    - King, Charles H., 1983-2000 (Box 52)
    - Ladd, Craig, 1983-2001 (Box 52)
    - Leemon, Donald (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 1983-2001 (Box 52)
      - Photographs (Box 52)
    - Lucas, William, 1983-1999 (Box 52)
    - Orms, Johnnie, 1983-2001 (Box 52)
    - Phelps, Billy, 1983-2001 (Box 53)
    - Putnam, Charles L., 1983-2000 (Box 53)
    - Rathgeber, William, 1983-2001 (Box 53)
    - Smith, George B., 1983-2000 (Box 53)
    - Stephens, Royce, 1983-2000 (Box 53)
    - Stone, Ronald E., 1983-2001 (Box 53)
    - Stuber, Robert, 1983-2001 (Box 53)
    - Theis, Norbert, 1983-2000 (Box 54)
    - Vaughan, James A., 1983-1999 (Box 54)
    - Von Luehrte, Robert, 1983-2000 (Box 54)
    - Watkins, Bernard, 1999-2000 (Box 54)
    - Weaver, Robert P., 1983-1999 (Box 55)
    - Wells, Lloyd, 1983-1999 (Box 55)
    - Wheaton, Lowell, 1983-2000 (Box 55)
    - Williams, Leland V.
      - 1983-1998 (Box 55)
      - 1998-2000 (Box 55)
    - Winter, Richard, 1983-1999 (Box 55)
    - Wurgel, Richard, 1983-1999 (Box 55)
  - Subject files
    - General (reproductions of photos, maps, and other documents, in spiral bound volumes assembled by Hirst and identified by letter)
      - A-G (Box 56)
      - H-O (Box 57)
    - Airlift headquarters (Wiesbaden), 1988-2000 (Box 58)
    - Airlift postcard, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Bakersfield, California, project (Fruitvale Junior High School), 1995 (Box 58)
    - Berlin airlift commemorations
      - 1989 (Box 58)
      - 1994 (Box 58)
      - 1998 (Box 58)
      - 1999 (Box 58)
        - General (Box 58)
        - Program (Box 58)
        - Press coverage (Box 58)
    - Berlin Airlift Historical Foundation, 1993-2003 (Box 59)
    - Berlin Airlift Memorial anniversary, 2001 (Box 59)
    - Berlin Airlift Veterans Association, 1985-2004 (Box 59)
    - Berlin, miscellaneous
      - 1984-1989 (Box 59)
      - 1990-1993 (Box 59)
      - 1994-2002 (Box 59)
    - British Berlin Airlift Association, 1995-2004 (Box 60)
    - Erding (Bayern), crash site, 1998-1999 (Box 60)
    - Facilities, U.S. Air Force Europe, undated (Box 60)
    - Families of airmen
      - 1983-1992 (Box 60)
      - 1993 (Box 60)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 60)
      - 1998 (Box 60)
      - 1999 (Box 60)
      - 2000 (Box 60)
      - 2001 (Box 60)
      - 2002 (Box 60)
      - 2003 (Box 60)
    - Farris, Merle, 1981-2004 (Box 60)
    - Fassberg (Royal Air Force station), 1983-2003 (Box 60)
    - France (airlift veterans), 1998-1999 (Box 61)
    - Galaxy Tours, 1999 (Box 61)
    - German casualties, 1988-2004 (Box 61)
    - Grossengottern (Thüringen), crash site, 1998-2000 (Box 61)
    - Haberland, Gerhard (crash survivor), 1988-2001 (Box 61)
    - Halvorsen, Gail, 1997-2001 (Box 61)
    - Historisches Museum Frankfurt/Main, 1998 (Box 61)
    - Kampe, Wolfgang, 2003 (Box 61)
    - Le May, Curtis, 1989 (Box 61)
    - Luftbrücke Chapter of the Airlift Association, e.V. (Rhein-Main Airbase), 1984-2004 (Box 61)
    - Marks, Raymond, 1999-2004 (Box 61)
    - News clippings (3 folders), 1998 (Box 62)
    - Oberpfaffenhofen (Bayern), crash site, 1999-2000 (Box 62)
    - Oberwiesenfeld Air Base (Bayern), photos, 1947 (Box 62)
    - Rath, George, 1996-2004 (Box 62)
    - Ravolzhausen (Hessen), crash site, 1999 (Box 62)
    - Rhein-Main Airbase
      - 1984-1992 (Box 62)
      - 1993-2004 (Box 62)
      - 50th anniversary of Berlin Airlift, 1998 (Box 62)
      - Base closure, 1999-2005 (Box 62)
      - Maps (Box 62)
      - Müller, Herbert (Box 62)
    - Rohden, Hans-Detlef von, 1986-1988 (Box 62)
    - Shmoo / CARE (mascot of CARE), 1994-2000 (Box 63)
    - Stiftung Luftbrückendank (Berlin), 1984-2004 (Box 63)
    - Wiesbaden Air Base, 1997-2002 (Box 63)
    - Shmoo / CARE (mascot of CARE), 1994-2000 (Box 63)
    - Stiftung Luftbrückendank (Berlin), 1984-2004 (Box 63)
    - Wiesbaden Air Base, 1997-2002 (Box 63)
- Normandy Operations Files, 1963-2004 (Box 64-99)
  Correspondence, manuscript drafts, newspaper clippings, newsletters, photographs, printed materials, and ephemera, arranged alphabetically within each subseries.
  - Advanced Landing Groups, summary binders (Folder 64-65)
    - Association Franco-Américaine des Aérodromes Normands de la Neuvième Air-Force, 1983-2000 (Folder 64)
    - Azeville-Cardonville (Folder 64)
    - Carentan-Le Molay (Folder 65)
    - Lessay-Saint-Jean-de-Daye (Folder 65)
    - Saint Lambert-Tour en Bessin (Folder 65)
  - Advanced Landing Groups, by airfield (Folder 65)
    - Azeville (A-7), (2 folders) (Folder 65)
    - Beuzeville (A-6) (Folder 66)
    - Biniville (A-24), 1983-2003 (Folder 66)
    - Bolleville (A-25), 1983-1998 (Folder 66)
    - Brucheville (A-16), 1993-2004 (Folder 66)
    - Cardonville (A-3), 1984-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 66)
    - Carentan (A-10), 1982-2004 (Folder 66)
    - Carentan (A-10)(continued), 1982-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 67)
    - Chippelle (A-5), 1982-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 67)
    - Colleville-sur-Mer (A-22), 1984-2002 (Folder 67)
    - Cretteville (A-14), 1984-2004 (Folder 67)
    - Cretteville (A-14)(continued), 1984-2004 (Folder 68)
    - Criqueville (A-2), 1983-2003; (2 folders) (Folder 68)
    - Deux Jumeaux (A-4), 1984-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 68)
    - Gorges (A-26), 1984-2002 (Folder 69)
    - La Vieille (A-19), 1983-1998 (Folder 69)
    - Le Molay (A-9), 1975-1998; (2 folders) (Folder 69)
    - Lessay (A-20), 1984-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 69)
    - Lignerolles (A-12), 1985-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 70)
    - Maupertus (A-15), 1985-2003; (3 folders) (Folder 70)
    - Méautis (A-17), 1983-2004 (Folder 70)
    - Picauville (A-8 and A-8N), 1983-2004; (4 folders) (Folder 71)
    - Poupeville (ELS), 1983-1997 (Folder 72)
    - Querqueville (A-23), 1988-1998 (Folder 72)
    - Saint-Jean-de-Daye (A-18), 1983-1998 (Folder 72)
    - Saint-Lambert (A-11), 1983-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 72)
    - Saint-Laurent (A-21), 1983-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 72)
    - Saint-Pierre-du-Mont (A-1), 1983-2004; (2 folders) (Folder 73)
    - Tour-en-Bessin (A-13), 1976-2004; (3 folders) (Folder 73)
  - Correspondence (individual and by towns) (Folder 73)
    - Air Force Historical Research Agency, 1995-1996 (Folder 73)
    - Ambrose, Stephen A., 1983-1997 (Folder 74)
    - Belin, Philippe, 2003-2004 (Folder 74)
    - Benamou, Jean-Pierre, 1990-2004 (Folder 74)
    - Blake, Steve, 1985-2004 (Folder 74)
    - Bouvier-Muller, Béatrice, 2003-2004 (Folder 74)
    - Chedal-Anglay, Jean-Pierre (Folder 74)
      - 1969-1993 (Folder 74)
      - 1994-2000 (Folder 74)
    - Chuinard, Rémy, 1992 (Folder 74)
    - Cities and towns (Folder 75:)
      - General (Folder 75)
      - Barneville, 1983-2002 (Folder 75)
      - Bayeux, 1990-1994 (Folder 75)
      - Beaumont-Hague, 1994-2001 (Folder 75)
      - Bienassis, 1993-1997 (Folder 75)
      - Boutteville, 1997-2001 (Folder 75)
      - Bricqueville, 1997 (Folder 75)
      - Canisy, 1998-1999 (Folder 75)
      - Carpiquet, 1994 (Folder 75)
      - Castillon, 1997 (Folder 75)
      - Cherbourg, 1994-2004 (Folder 75)
      - Colombières, 1997-2000 (Folder 75)
      - Ecrammeville, 1997 (Folder 75)
      - Englesqueville, 2004 (Folder 75)
      - Flamanville, 1997 (Folder 75)
      - Gréville-Hague, 1997-2001 (Folder 75)
      - Gruchy, 2002 (Folder 75)
      - Isigny-sur-Mer, 1963-1996 (Folder 75)
      - Longueville, 1997 (Folder 75)
      - Nacqueville, 1994-2002 (Folder 75)
      - Pointe-du-Hoc, 1984-1993 (Folder 75)
      - Saint-Germain-du-Pert, 1997-1998 (Folder 75)
      - Saint-Pierre-Eglise, 2003 (Folder 76)
      - Saint-Sauveur-Lendelin, 1997 (Folder 76)
      - Saint-Vaast-la-Hougue, 1999 (Folder 76)
      - Sainte-Mère-Eglise, 2002-2003 (Folder 76)
      - Valognes, 1997-1998 (Folder 76)
      - Vaubadon, 1997-2003 (Folder 76)
      - Ver-sur-Mer, 1996 (Folder 76)
      - Vierville-sur-Mer, 1993-2004 (Folder 76)
      - Yvetot-Brocage, 1997-2004 (Folder 76)
    - Coipel, François, 2003-2004 (Folder 76)
    - Cordelle, Yves, 1989 (Folder 76)
    - Delahaye, Patrick, 1992-1997 (Folder 76)
    - Dube, Noel, 1990-2004 (Folder 76)
    - Dufour, Luc, 2003 (Folder 76)
    - Dungey, Kenneth, 1991-1994 (Folder 76)
    - Dupont, Jean-Pierre (Folder 76)
      - 1997-1999 (Folder 76)
      - 2000-2003 (Folder 76)
    - Elliott, Lawrence, 1989 (Folder 76)
    - Ethell, Jeffrey, 1991-1994 (Folder 76)
    - Etienvre, Victor, 1974-1991
    - Friesen, Hans Carl von, 1983-1996 (Folder 76)
    - Godier, Jean-Marie, 2004 (Folder 76)
    - Goucovitch, Bertrand, 2003-2005 (Folder 76)
    - Greenwood, John, 1988-1992 (Folder 77)
    - Gross, Clayton Kelly, 1995-2003 (Folder 77)
    - Hallé, Nicolas, 2003 (Folder 77)
    - Hamel, André, 1996-2004 (Folder 77)
    - Hamilton, David, 1995-1996 (Folder 77)
    - Hardelay, Michel, 1984-1994 (Folder 77)
    - Hautefeuille, Roland, 2004 (Folder 77)
    - Heintz, André, 1997-2004 (Folder 77)
    - Helias, Claude, 1994-2000 (Folder 77)
    - Henshall, Philip, 2003 (Folder 77)
    - Higham, Robin, 1996-1999 (Folder 77)
    - Jaworski, Leonard, 1988-2004 (Folder 77)
    - Jutras, Philippe, 1980-2004 (Folder 77)
    - Karpen, Raymond, 1985-1988 (Folder 78)
    - Kirchner, Marie, 2003-2004 (Folder 78)
    - La Cacheux, Geneviève, 1988-2002 (Folder 78)
    - Landemaine, Fernand, 2003-2004 (Folder 78)
    - Livingston, Guy, 1994-1996 (Folder 78)
    - Moran, Patrick, 1992-1993 (Folder 78)
    - Osborne, James R., 1986-1993 (Folder 78)
    - Patton, Ralph, 1992-1994 (Folder 78)
    - Petri, Paul, 1992 (Folder 78)
    - Rainfroy, Michel, 1992-1997 (Folder 78)
    - Rivers, Joseph, 1983-2000 (Folder 78)
    - Rock, Marjorie, 1997 (Folder 78)
    - Signs, William, 1996-1997 (Folder 78)
    - Sisson, Juliane, 1997-2000 (Folder 78)
    - Sochocki, Casimier, 1988-2004 (Folder 78)
    - Tate, Don (Stars and Stripes), 1989 (Folder 78)
    - Thierot, Henri, 1992-2001 (Folder 79)
    - Toliver, Raymond, 1977-2004 (Folder 79)
    - Triboulet, Raymond, 1983-1994 (Folder 79)
    - Twohig, Edward, 1994-2004 (Folder 79)
    - Valavielle, Michel de, 1982-1991 (Folder 79)
    - Vatin, Jean, 1983-1992 (Folder 79)
    - Woelffel, Sandrine, 2003-2004 (Folder 79)
  - Subject files (including Normandy treks) (Folder 79)
    - Advanced Landing Groups (Folder 79)
      - General, 1986-1995 (Folder 79)
      - Photographs, 1992-1993 (Folder 79)
    - American Sons of Normandy, 2003 (Folder 79)
    - Ardenne Abbey Library, 1994 (Folder 79)
    - Association Franco-Américaine des Aérodromes Normands de la Neuvième Air-Force, 1986-2002 (Folder 79)
    - Aviation engineers, 1984-1988 (Folder 79)
    - Background research, general, undated (Folder 79)
    - Background research, general, undated (continued) (Folder 80)
    - Bradley, Gen. Omar (Folder 80)
      - General (Folder 80)
      - Omar Bradley Memorial/Carolee Hazlet (Folder 80)
    - Canadians, 2003-2004 (Folder 80)
    - Comité d'Action de la Résistance, 1984 (Folder 80)
    - C.S.S. Alabama, 2001 (Folder 80)
    - D-Day: Counterintelligence Corps, 1991-1994 (Folder 80)
    - D-Day: 50th anniversary commemorations, 1991-1994 (Folder 80)
    - D-Day: Newspaper coverage of 50th anniversary (Folder 80)
    - D-Day: Navy, 1991-1994 (Folder 81)
    - D-Day Airborne Armada, 1993 (Folder 81)
    - Ecausseville (potential museum site), 1994-2003 (Folder 81)
    - Ehrgott, General Herbert (Chief of Command, 9th Engineer Command) (Folder 81)
    - Engineer Aviation Battalions, 1986-1993 (Folder 81)
    - Engineer Aviation Battalions, 1986-1993 (Folder 81)
    - First Army Headquarters (FUSA), 1997-2000 (Folder 81)
    - Guide to the Ninth Air Force Normandy Air Patches, June - September 1944, by Ronald M.A. Hirst (Folder 81)
      - Bibliography (Folder 81)
      - Biographical sketches (Folder 81)
      - Cover and introduction (Folder 81)
      - 1988 revision (Folder 81)
    - Insignias, 1983-1984 (Folder 81)
    - Liaison squadrons, 1987-2004 (Folder 82)
    - Maps, undated; (2 folders) (Folder 82)
    - "Marauder Men Return" reunion, 1992 (Folder 82)
    - Mayors: Manche-Calvados, 1992-2003 (Folder 82)
    - Memorials, Private, 2002-2003 (Folder 83)
    - Military Railway Service, 1997 (Folder 83)
    - Military units, 1983-2004 (Folder 83)
      - 3rd Radio Battalion, 1996-2004 (Folder 83)
      - 8th Air Force, 2002 (Folder 83)
      - 12th Army Group, 1996-2004 (Folder 83)
      - 19th Tactical Air Command (Folder 83)
      - 29th Infantry Division, 1994 (Folder 83)
      - 36th Fighter Group, 1988-1997 (Folder 83)
      - 50th Troop Carrier Wing, 1988-1992 (Folder 83)
      - 52nd Troop Carrier Wing, 1983-2000 (Folder 83)
      - 53rd Troop Carrier Wing, 1983-2002 (Folder 83)
        - General (Folder 83)
        - Greenville Gliders (Folder 83)
        - General Maurice Beach (Folder 83)
      - 70th Fighter Wing, 1983-1993 (Folder 83)
      - 71st Fighter Wing, 1984-1996 (Folder 83)
      - 84th Fighter Wing, 1988-1996 (Folder 83)
      - 100th Fighter Wing, 1983-1999 (Folder 83)
      - 147th Engineer Combat Battalion, 1993-1994 (Folder 83)
      - 261st Medical Battalion, 1994 (Folder 83)
      - 302nd Signal Operations Battalion, 1996-2002 (Folder 83)
      - 303rd Fighter Wing, 1983 (Folder 83)
      - 344th Battle Group, 2003 (Folder 84)
      - 354th Fighter Group, 1994-1995 (Folder 84)
      - 365th Fighter Group, 1993-1995 (Folder 84)
      - 366th Fighter Group, 1988-1990 (Folder 84)
      - 367th Fighter Group, 1984-1995 (Folder 84)
      - 368th Fighter Group, 1987-1993 (Folder 84)
      - 395th Signal Company (Aviation), 1997-2003 (Folder 84)